<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Companion Object Bootcamp. Learn to build quality Android apps, for free.</title>
    <link>http://bootcamp.companionobject.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Companion Object Bootcamp. Learn to build quality Android apps, for free.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 16:09:20 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://bootcamp.companionobject.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About COB</title>
      <link>http://bootcamp.companionobject.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 16:09:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bootcamp.companionobject.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Companion Object Bootcamp is a free, intense, and focused educational program in mobile DevOps, aimed for anyone developing Android apps willing to decrease development cost and time-to-market while improving the overall quality and user satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our series of up-to-date, relevant, detailed and approachable courses are designed to help teams and individuals around the globe developing Android apps to eliminate inefficiencies in their development processes, implement and improve neglected yet crucial aspects of app delivery such as test automation, fragmentation, error reporting or monitoring, and in result increase chances for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companion Object Bootcamp aims to be the one-stop-shop for engineers, developers, team leads and project managers to update themselves on best practices of all aspects of mobile app development outside of feature development. This includes but is not limited to topics like mobile testing, build pipelines, flavors, A/B testing, deployment, monitoring, analytics, error reporting and user acquisition. We want to help implement all the necessary support processes in a way that increases the amount of time teams can spend on feature development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companion Object Bootcamp is a completely free initiative run by &lt;a href=&#34;http://companionobject.com&#34;&gt;Companion Object&lt;/a&gt;, an Android consultancy company specialising in mobile DevOps, which includes often-neglected and always-hard aspects of Android app development, such as mobile testing automation, fragmentation, product line engineering, build tools, and monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>